<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?><Response xmlns="http://data.fcc.gov/spectrum-view/services" status="OK"><Criteria><SearchCriterion field="frequencyFrom" value="600"/><SearchCriterion field="frequencyTo" value="900"/></Criteria><SpectrumBands page="1" rowPerPage="1000" totalRows="15" lastUpdate="Jul 7, 2014"><SpectrumBand id="27"><lowerBand>512</lowerBand><upperBand>608</upperBand><bandDesc>This band is used in the Broadcast Television Service, the Low Power Auxiliary Service, and the Low Power Television (LPTV) Service (including TV Translator, TV Booster, and Class A Stations). Operation of unlicensed Part 15 Devices is permitted between 512 and 608 MHz.</bandDesc></SpectrumBand><SpectrumBand id="28"><lowerBand>608</lowerBand><upperBand>614</upperBand><bandDesc>This band is used in the Wireless Medical Telemetry Service (WMTS) and the Radioastronomy Service. This band is allocated for both Federal and Non-Federal use.</bandDesc></SpectrumBand><SpectrumBand id="29"><lowerBand>614</lowerBand><upperBand>698</upperBand><bandDesc>This band is used in the Broadcast Television Service, the Low Power Auxiliary Service, and the Low Power Television (LPTV) Service (including TV Translator, TV Booster, and Class A Stations). Operation of unlicensed Part 15 Devices is permitted between 614 and 698 MHz.</bandDesc></SpectrumBand><SpectrumBand id="30"><lowerBand>698</lowerBand><upperBand>763</upperBand><bandDesc>This band is used in the 700 MHz Service, the Low Power Auxiliary Service, and the Low Power Television (LPTV) Service (including TV Translator, TV Booster, and Class A Stations). Operation of unlicensed Part 15 devices is permitted between 698 and 763 MHz.</bandDesc></SpectrumBand><SpectrumBand id="31"><lowerBand>763</lowerBand><upperBand>775</upperBand><bandDesc>This band is used in the Low Power Auxiliary Service, the Low Power Television (LPTV) Service (including TV Translator, TV Booster, and Class A Stations), and the Public Safety Service. Operation of unlicensed Part 15 devices is permitted between 763 and 775 MHz.</bandDesc></SpectrumBand><SpectrumBand id="32"><lowerBand>775</lowerBand><upperBand>793</upperBand><bandDesc>This band is used in the 700 MHz Service, the Low Power Auxiliary Service, and the Low Power Television (LPTV) Service (including TV Translator, TV Booster, and Class A Stations). Operation of unlicensed Part 15 devices is permitted between 775 and 793 MHz.</bandDesc></SpectrumBand><SpectrumBand id="33"><lowerBand>793</lowerBand><upperBand>805</upperBand><bandDesc>This band is used in the Low Power Auxiliary Service, the Low Power Television (LPTV) Service (including TV Translator, TV Booster, and Class A Stations), and the Public Safety Service. Operation of unlicensed Part 15 devices is permitted between 793 and 805 MHz.</bandDesc></SpectrumBand><SpectrumBand id="34"><lowerBand>805</lowerBand><upperBand>806</upperBand><bandDesc>This band is used in the 700 MHz Band Service, the Low Power Auxiliary Service, and the Low Power Television (LPTV) Service (including TV Translator, TV Booster, and Class A Stations). Operation of unlicensed Part 15 Devices is permitted between 805 and 806 MHz.</bandDesc></SpectrumBand><SpectrumBand id="35"><lowerBand>806</lowerBand><upperBand>809</upperBand><bandDesc>This band is used in the Public Safety Radio Service. Operation of unlicensed Part 15 Devices is permitted between 806 and 809 MHz.</bandDesc></SpectrumBand><SpectrumBand id="36"><lowerBand>809</lowerBand><upperBand>849</upperBand><bandDesc>This band is used in the Business/Industrial Land Transportation Service, the Cellular Radiotelephone Service, the Public Safety Radio Service, and the Specialized Mobile Radio (SMR) Service. Operation of unlicensed Part 15 Devices is permitted between 809 and 849 MHz.</bandDesc></SpectrumBand><SpectrumBand id="37"><lowerBand>849</lowerBand><upperBand>851</upperBand><bandDesc>This band is used in the Commercial Air-Ground Radiotelephone Service. Operation of unlicensed Part 15 Devices is permitted between 849 and 851 MHz.</bandDesc></SpectrumBand><SpectrumBand id="38"><lowerBand>851</lowerBand><upperBand>854</upperBand><bandDesc>This band is used in the Public Safety Radio Service. Operation of unlicensed Part 15 Devices is permitted is permitted between 851 and 854 MHz.</bandDesc></SpectrumBand><SpectrumBand id="39"><lowerBand>854</lowerBand><upperBand>894</upperBand><bandDesc>This band is used in the Business/Industrial Land Transportation Service, the Cellular Radiotelephone Service, the Public Safety Radio Service, and the Specialized Mobile Radio (SMR) Service. Operation of unlicensed Part 15 Devices is permitted between 854 and 894 MHz.</bandDesc></SpectrumBand><SpectrumBand id="40"><lowerBand>894</lowerBand><upperBand>896</upperBand><bandDesc>This band is used in the Commercial Air-Ground Radiotelephone Service. Operation of unlicensed Part 15 Devices is permitted is permitted between 894 and 896 MHz.</bandDesc></SpectrumBand><SpectrumBand id="41"><lowerBand>896</lowerBand><upperBand>901</upperBand><bandDesc>This band is used in the Business/Industrial Land Transportation Service, and the Specialized Mobile Radio (SMR) Service. Operation of unlicensed Part 15 Devices is permitted between 896 and 901 MHz.</bandDesc></SpectrumBand></SpectrumBands></Response>